{
    "id": "f2054edce1214db38eb54032068da241",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is not ………………. clever as his brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be punished ………………. he is guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A fool …………… his money are soon parted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was not punished …………….. he was guilty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "as though",
                "as if"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He worked hard ……………… he might pass the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "that",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Give every man thy ear, ……………… few thy voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for him ………………… the clock struck seven.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "unless",
                "up to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the prize ……………… you deserve it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been a year ……………… I saw him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Hardly had he reached the platform ……………….. the train arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did he see the tiger ………………. he fainted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "then",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. you do not apologize, I shall punish you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}